Collective, not Exclusive
集体性 而不是排外
Actually I was like a mother to them from My very childhood
实际上在我很小的时候我就像个母亲对待他们
When My father, mother went to jail I was, first time I was about, I think five and a half years of age
当我父母第一次进监狱 我想我大概五岁半左右
So I had all the keys of the house in My little frock thing and I used to carry all the duties like a grand mother
所以我将家中所有的钥匙放进我小小的礼服 我曾经像个伟大的母亲一样担起所有的责任
I never felt lost. I mean, My life is on the whole is very collective. By temperament I am extremely collective
我从未感到迷失 我的意思是 我的整个生活非常的合群 我非常有集体性
I can live anywhere. I can sleep anywhere. I can live in the jungles. I have no problems with that. I am extremely collective
我可以住在任何地方 我可以睡在任何地方 我可以住在丛林中 对我来说没有问题 我非常有集体性
I am not exclusive by temperament from very childhood
从很小的时候我就不排外
I was very friendly with all the people in that area where we were living
我在我生活的地方和所有人都非常友好
and My mother was known was Nirmala’s mother
我的母亲被称为Nirmala的母亲
Father was known was Nirmala’s father. So they said, We have lost our identity because of Her.
父亲被称为Nirmala的父亲 所以他们说因为她我们失去了自己的身份
So I was a very friendly person. I never felt lonely
所以我是个很友好的人 我从未感到孤独
and when I am with Myself I am never lonely at all. I enjoy Myself very much
并且当我独自一人 我从来不觉得孤单 我很享受自己